So let's say that we're not going to McDonald's or a fast food place at a place like that.
因此，假设我们不会去麦当劳或类似地方的快餐店。
You don't need a waiter let's say we're going to a place where there is a waiter and you're going to
你不需要服务员，假设我们要去一个有服务员的地方，你要去
sit down sometimes we call this a sit down restaurant.
坐下有时我们称之为坐下餐厅。
OK or we sometimes say that we're dining in but we often say it's a sit down restaurant which means
好的，或者我们有时会说我们正在用餐，但我们经常说这是一家坐下来的餐厅，这意味着
it's a little bit more formal when you walk into the restaurant.
当你走进餐厅时，它会更正式一些。
The person at the door is actually not the waiter.
门口的人其实不是服务员。
Probably that person may be called a host or a hostess hostess a man and a hostess is a woman waiter
可能那个人可能被称为主人或女主人女主人是男人，女主人是女服务员
is a man waitress is a woman host hostess waiter waitress.
是男服务员 是女招待 女招待 服务员 女服务员。
OK.
好的。
Now this person the host or hostess is the person who greets you at the door takes you to your table
现在这个人，主人或女主人是在门口迎接你的人，带你到你的餐桌
or maybe checks your reservation, a reservation means that you have called beforehand to
或者可能会检查您的预订预订 预订意味着您已事先致电
to actually get a table.
真正得到一张桌子。
Right.
正确的。
And that's very simple.
这很简单。
You would just say you would call the restaurant and say I'd like to book or reserve a table for
你只会说你会打电话给餐厅说我想预订或预订一张桌子
six under and then your family name maybe Jones under Jones or I'd like to book a table for six.
六下，然后你的姓可能是琼斯下的琼斯，或者我想订一张六人桌。
Then they'll say what time.
然后他们会说什么时间。
And you say oh seven thirty.
你说哦七点三十。
OK.
好的。
And what's the name Jones if you want to say it altogether you can.
如果你想完全说出来，琼斯的名字是什么。
But the person on the phone will probably miss some details if you say I'd like to book or reserve a
但是，如果您说我想预订或预订电话，电话中的人可能会错过一些细节
table for six under Jones at seven thirty.
琼斯七点三十分，六人桌。
They're writing all that down.
他们正在写下这一切。
So just say a little bit first and you could even start with the very beginning.
所以先说一点，你甚至可以从头开始。
Hello.
你好。
I'd like to book a table for six.
我想订一张六人桌。
OK.
好的。
Short what time.
短什么时间。
Seven thirty.
七点半。
OK.
好的。
A Table For Six at seven thirty.
七点三十分的六人餐桌。
And what's the name.
还有叫什么名字。
It's JONES OK.
琼斯没事。
Great.
伟大的。
So it's a table for six at seven thirty under Jones.
所以这是一张六点七点三十分在琼斯之下的桌子。
Yep that's correct.
是的，这是正确的。
OK.
好的。
Thank you very much.
非常感谢。
That's very simple.
这很简单。
OK.
好的。
When you walk into the restaurant then if you have that reservation one common question that the host
当您走进餐厅时，如果您有预订，主人会问一个常见问题
or hostess may ask you this person may ask you is do you have a reservation.
或者女主人可能会问你这个人可能会问你是否有预订。
Do you have a reservation.
你有预约吗。
And the answer if it's yes it's a yes I have a table for six and you'd say the same information they
如果是的话，答案是肯定的，我有一张六人桌，你会说和他们一样的信息
might say OK what's the name.
可能会说 OK 叫什么名字。
Yes I have a reservation at seven thirty.
是的，我在七点三十分有一个预订。
What's the name.
什么名字。
It's JONES OK.
琼斯没事。
Great.
伟大的。
Now if they don't ask this question or if you don't have a reservation and you go in and they say Do
现在，如果他们不问这个问题，或者如果你没有预订，你进去，他们说做
you have a reservation.
你有一个预订。
You say no.
你说不。
Or they ask you directly how many how many people or how many how many.
或者他们直接问你有多少人或多少人。
Or how many people then you just say how many people we have six six people or we need or I need.
或者有多少人，然后你只说我们有多少人，我们有六个六个人，或者我们需要或我需要。
OK.
好的。
We need a table for six A Table For Six.
我们需要一张六人桌六人桌。
We're at the restaurant.
我们在餐厅。
Maybe you have to wait a few minutes.
也许你必须等待几分钟。
They might say Oh well unfortunately we don't have a table right now.
他们可能会说哦，很遗憾，我们现在没有桌子。
There is a ten minute wait.
有十分钟的等待。
Is that OK.
那样行吗。
Yeah that's all right.
是的，没关系。
That's fine.
没关系。
There's a ten minute wait.
有十分钟的等待。
Well let's just start the situation fresh and make it simpler by saying we just have two people I want
那么让我们只是让情况重新开始，说我们只有两个我想要的人，让它变得更简单
to do it a little bit simpler.
让它更简单一点。
We've done the reservation thing so let's just say we walk into the restaurant there's a hostess and
我们已经完成了预订，所以假设我们走进餐厅有一位女主人和
she just says how many.
她只是说有多少。
And it's me and another person and I say a table for two please table a table for two please.
是我和另一个人，我说一张两人桌，请一张两人桌。
And I should actually have a comma there a table for two please.
我实际上应该有一个逗号，有一张两人桌。
And she could ask me and brought a reservation but we've set a table for two.
她可以问我并带来预订，但我们已经为两人安排了一张桌子。
We know how to do that.
我们知道该怎么做。
All right.
好的。
Now I want to make a specific request I say.
现在我想提出一个具体的要求。
She says ok and I say do you.
她说好的，我说你呢。
Do you have any seats or tables by the window by the window.
你有靠窗的座位或靠窗的桌子吗？
Do you have any seats or tables by the window.
你有靠窗的座位或桌子吗？ 不要说座位或桌子。
Say do you have any seats by the window.
说你有靠窗的座位吗？
Do you have any tables by a window or whatever you want to say OK.
你有没有靠窗的桌子或任何你想说的好。
Yeah we do.
是的，我们有。
We do.
我们的确是。
Or let me check.
或者让我检查一下。
Let me check.
让我检查一下。
Maybe she doesn't know.
也许她不知道。
She might say Let me check.
她可能会说让我检查一下。
Let me check.
让我检查一下。
Let me see.
让我看看。
Yes we do.
是的，我们这样做。
Right this way.
这边请。
Right this way please follow me and then I usually say Oh great great.
就这样，请跟我来，然后我通常会说哦，太好了。
Then I follow her or him if it's a host.
然后，如果是主持人，我会跟随她或他。
OK.
好的。
So that's the first part we know how to do a reservation when they ask how many we say a table for two.
所以当他们问我们说一张两人桌有多少时，这是我们知道如何进行预订的第一部分。
We could just say two.
我们只能说两个。
And then if we need to make a specific request we say Oh and could we get a table by the window.
然后如果我们需要提出一个特定的要求，我们会说哦，我们可以在窗边找一张桌子吗？
Could we get a table next to the bar or far away from the bar or whatever you want to say.
我们可以在酒吧旁边或远离酒吧或您想说的任何地方找一张桌子吗？